<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Evander Grimveil</title>
    <link>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Evander Grimveil</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024 Evander Grimveil</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dark Artifacts: Lessons Learned from the Field</title>
      <link>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/dark-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/dark-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the last few months, I’ve had the privilege—and the challenge—of working with some of the most dangerous relics documented to date. These objects, steeped in curses, represent millennia of arcane history, yet we’re only beginning to understand the depth of their power and risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One critical lesson is that stability can hinge on even the smallest factors: a slight increase in ambient magical energy can activate curses unexpectedly. My team’s newest containment protocol, which we developed based on recent artifact failures, emphasizes double-enchantment barriers, an innovation that we hope will prevent further &amp;lsquo;field surprises.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethical Summoner: Navigating Responsibility in Dark Arts</title>
      <link>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/the-ethical-summoner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/the-ethical-summoner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Working in summoning and conjuration often feels like walking a razor&amp;rsquo;s edge. The thrill of channeling powerful, ancient forces is undeniable, but so too is the responsibility that comes with it. In my recent research on conjured entities, I’ve realized that ethical practices must adapt to the changing landscape of dark arts. This isn’t about wielding power but about understanding its true scope and ramifications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One area I’m currently focused on is the balance between control and autonomy when dealing with conjured beings. Traditional containment spells often impose harsh restrictions on entities, sometimes sparking unpredictable reactions. My team and I are developing &amp;lsquo;sympathetic conjurations,&amp;rsquo; which allow for a respectful balance of autonomy, mitigating the risk of volatility while maintaining control.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hex Transference: Ancient Techniques, Modern Challenges</title>
      <link>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/hex-transference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/hex-transference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the world of dark arts, curse transference remains one of the most elusive and complex phenomena to master. Recently, I’ve been revisiting some ancient techniques from the Grimoire of Ebon Shadows, and while many of these methods seem arcane and outdated, they carry a wisdom that our modern techniques sometimes lack. However, adapting these rituals for current use is a task riddled with hurdles—primarily the unpredictability of hex potency when transferred across different mediums.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relic Ethics: Where Do We Draw the Line?</title>
      <link>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/relic-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clusravin.github.io/hugo-theme-live-cv/posts/relic-ethics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The allure of cursed artifacts is undeniable—each relic carries a unique energy, a story etched in dark enchantments. But as I’ve delved deeper into artifact containment research, one question repeatedly haunts my mind: Are there some relics too dangerous to keep, even in the name of knowledge?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently examined a hex-bound relic known as the Veilstone Chalice, a cup steeped in a curse that seems to drain vitality from anything nearby. Containing it required an immense, double-layered protection protocol, and even then, it showed an unpredictable resonance with nearby magic. This raises a crucial ethical dilemma: At what point does the risk to practitioners, even to bystanders, outweigh the benefits of studying such objects?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
